http://halcraft.com/policies/terms-of-service

Shop NEW ARRIVALS!Beads Bone BeadsCeramic Beads Glazed Ceramic BeadsPeruvian Ceramic BeadsCoral BeadsGlass Beads Chinese Seed BeadsCzech Fire Polished BeadsCzech Preciosa BeadsCzech Seed BeadsGlass Multi PacksGlass PearlsHand-blown Glass BeadsIndian Glass BeadsFreshwater PearlsHorn BeadsMetal BeadsResin BeadsSemi-precious Beads Cabochon BeadsDruzy BeadsMeaningful BeadsMulti Packs BeadsNatural Moonstone BeadsNatural Turquoise BeadsPrecious Gemstone BeadsShell BeadsSliderSwarovski® CrystalsWood Beads Costa Rican Rosewood BeadsPhilippine Wood BeadsCharms & Connectors ConnectorsGold Tone CharmsMulti Pack CharmsPatina, Brass, & Copper CharmsRhinestone CharmsSilver Tone CharmsPendants CZ-Cubic Zirconia PendantsGlass PendantsMetal PendantsPearl PendantsPendant BundlesPendant KitsSemi-precious / Stone PendantsShell PendantsTasselsJewelry BraceletsEarringsNecklacesRingsFindings BailCapsChainsClaspsCrimpsHead & Eye PinsStringing Materials ChainCordingWiresTools, Storage & Display AdhesivesDisplayJewelry Gift BagJewelry Gift BoxStorageToolDIY DIY InspirationThe BasicsSizing Your JewelryVideo TutorialsBlog Design InspirationDesign on a DimeBeads Out & AboutStep-By-Step TutorialsPretty PalettesMonday MakeBeading for BeginnersGift CardWholesale/Discounts
Free Shipping on Orders of $50 within the US.
Menu
0
Shop
Beads
Bone Beads
Ceramic Beads
Coral Beads
Freshwater Pearls
TERMS AND CONDITIONS USER AGREEMENT
Welcome to the website of HALCRAFT USA, INC., a New York corporation with an office at 60 South MacQuesten Parkway, Mount Vernon, New York 10550-1741, hereinafter referred to as HALCRAFT. Throughout the site, the terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to HALCRAFT.
These Terms and Conditions set forth the terms and conditions which govern your purchase of any beads and all of the other items displayed and offered for sale on the website, www.halcraftcollection.com., also referred to in these Terms and Conditions as the “Website”.
The Website offers the goods and services described on the Website, and in every instance those services and goods are subject to these Terms and Conditions set forth in this document. HALCRAFT reserves the right to change these Terms and Conditions at any time without prior notice. Any new pages, features or tools added to the Website at any time in the future will be subject to these Terms and Conditions.
Any payment you make on our Website to purchase a product or service offered on our Website will be processed by Shopify, Inc. Shopify Inc. is an independent entity which has contracted with us to provide credit card processing for the Website.
If you purchase any goods or services offered on the Website, or if you otherwise use the Website, that action will indicate that you have agreed with all of the terms and conditions set out in these Terms and Conditions. The term “you” refers to any user of the Website, without regard to whether you are an individual, a business, a vendor, a merchant, a browser or anyone else. PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT CAREFULLY BEFORE PURCHASING ANY GOODS OR SERVICES OFFERED ON THE WEBSITE OR BEFORE YOU OTHERWISE USE OUR WEBSITE. YOU MAY PURCHASE PRODUCTS OR SERVICES OFFERED ON THIS WEBSITE ONLY IF YOU ARE NOT A “MINOR’ IN THE STATE, PROVINCE OR OTHER JURISDICTION IN WHICH YOU LIVE OR IF YOU HAVE AGREED WITH YOUR CREDIT CARD ISSUER TO PERMIT A MINOR TO USE YOUR CREDIT CARD.
1. Use of the Website
If you use the Website, you are representing and warranting that you are not a minor or are under the supervision of your parent or legal guardian when visiting and/or using the Website. Subject to these Terms and Conditions, the Website grants each user a limited, revocable, non-transferable and non-exclusive license to access and use the Website to display the Website on your internet browser only for the purpose of shopping for goods and services offered for sale on the Website. If you attempt to make or do make commercial use of any of the information on the Website or make use of the Website for the benefit of the third parties without the advance, written permission of HALCRAFT, the limited license granted in this paragraph will be deemed to have been revoked without requiring notice to you. You shall not reproduce, distribute, display, sell, lease, transmit, create derivative works from, translate, modify, disassemble or de-compile any content of this Website, including illustrations and the code used to create this Website.
In addition to other prohibitions as set forth in these Terms and Conditions, you are prohibited from using the Website or its content: (a) for any unlawful purpose; (b) to solicit others to perform or participate in any unlawful acts; (c) to violate any international, federal, provincial or state regulations, rules, laws, or local ordinances; (d) to infringe upon or violate our intellectual property rights or the intellectual property rights of others; (e) to be libelous, threatening, defamatory, obscene or indecent or to harass, abuse, insult, harm, defame, slander, disparage, intimidate, or discriminate based on gender, sexual orientation, religion, ethnicity, race, age, national origin, or disability; (f) to submit false or misleading information; (g) to upload or transmit any code, cookies, bugs, viruses, worms, trap doors, Trojan horses or other malware or malicious code, without regard to your intent; (h) to collect or track the personal information of others; (i) to spam, phish, pharm, pretext, spider, crawl, or scrape; (j) for any obscene or immoral purpose; or (k) to interfere with or circumvent the security features of the Website or its credit card processor (Shopify, Inc.) or any related website, other websites, or the Internet. If in their sole discretion, HALCRAFT, the Website Administrator or Shopify, Inc. determines that your conduct violates any of these Terms and Conditions or is harmful to interests of HALCRAFT, the Website or Shopify, Inc., HALCRAFT or the Website Administrator or Shopify, Inc. will have the right to refuse service, terminate your accounts, and/or cancel your orders without prior notice.
Your password and other account identification have been chosen and assigned to you in order for you to be able to access and use certain portions of the Website. Each time you log on to the Website, you will be deemed to be an authorized user subject to these Terms and Conditions. You are solely responsible for the use of the password and identification originally assigned to you to enable you to use the Website, without regard to whether such access is actually authorized by you. You will be responsible for all communications with the Website and for all obligations (including financial obligations) incurred through such access or use. You are totally responsible for protecting the security and confidentiality of the password and other identification criteria assigned to you. You will immediately notify the Website of any unauthorized use of your password or identification or any other breach or threatened breach of Website security. If you do notify the Website of a security breach, you must request a confirmation email that such notice was received by the Website. Such confirmation will be sent to the email address you will have provided in the notice of security breach.
We reserve the right to refuse service or refuse to sell any product or service to anyone at any time for any reason or no reason.
2. Reviews and Comments
The content of any submission or post you make to the Website, including information containing ideas, techniques, suggestions questions, reviews and other comments will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary information. By making a post or submission to the Website, you are agreeing to provide the Website and HALCRAFT with a royalty-free, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, and transferable license to use or reproduce the post or submission in any way whatsoever. This license shall include rights to use, copy, distribute, display, publish, perform, sell, lease, transmit, translate, modify and create derivative works from such post and submissions by any means and in any form. All the contents of any submission or post shall not be returned to you and you agree not to dispute any treatment or use of any post or submission.
You warrant that the content of any post or submission made by you is free and clear of Intellectual property right owned by any third party. HALCRAFT and the Website assume no liability for misuse of copyright or any other intellectual property rights of third parties in any post or submission made by you. You agree to defend and indemnify HALCRAFT and the Website against any losses, damages or legal fees incurred by HALCRAFT or the Website incurred because you have accidentally or intentionally breached the warranty set forth in this paragraph.
HALCRAFT and the Website shall have the right to use your name in connection with your posts and submissions to the website. You agree not to use a false email address or pretend to be someone other than yourself, or to mislead HALCRAFT and the Website as to the origin of any content in any post or submission. HALCRAFT and the Website will not be obligated to remove or edit any content you provide in a post or submission.
3. Copyright
All text, graphics, photographs, other images, button icons, audio clips, logos, slogans, trade names, trade styles, text and other contents on the Website (collectively, “Website Content”), belongs exclusively to HALCRAFT or its content suppliers. You may not use, reproduce, copy, modify, transmit, display, publish, sell, license, publicly perform, distribute or commercially exploit any of the Website Content. The use of data mining, robots, meta-tags or other data gathering and extraction tools on the Website is strictly prohibited. You may view and use the Website Content only for your personal use and for shopping and ordering on the site, and for no other purpose. You may not use Website Content (including any code, translator or compilation) in any manner which would disparage or discredit HALCRAFT or the Website. All software used on the Website (the “Software”) is the property of HALCRAFT and/or its Software suppliers. Software means and includes all object code, source code, compilations, translations and executable code. The Software is protected under United States laws and also under the laws of other countries and conventions. HALCRAFT and/or its Software suppliers will prosecute violators of law to the fullest extent possible.
4. Privacy Policy
HALCRAFT is committed to protecting the privacy and Personal Information of persons who use the Website. “Personal Information” is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. After you register as an account holder on the Website, you will be able to purchase products and services offered on the Website, and where provided on the Website, you may be able to download pictures and designs and to receive coupons or other premiums offered by HALCRAFT
In order for us to process and fulfill orders made through the Website, and to enable us to provide order shipping status, it is necessary for us to know some of your Personal Information; your name, mailing address and phone number. We will not share that Personal Information with third parties except as applicable law may require; and we will not sell your information to any third party.
We use Shopify, Inc., a well respected third party credit card processing company to handle all credit card charges and credits with regard to your transactions with the Website. Shopify, Inc. will have access to your personal information as well as to certain financial information; your credit card issuer, card number, expiration date and the security code you use to purchase items from the Website. HALCRAFT will not have access to your credit card information or other financial information; we only receive notification when a payment has been received or refunded.
Shopify, Inc. has represented to us that it will not share your Personal Information with third parties except as applicable law may require, and it will not sell your information to any third party. The Privacy Policy of Shopify, Inc. can be found on line at https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy and that policy will govern your credit card transactions. To the extent there are any differences between the terms of our Privacy Policy and that of Shopify, Inc., the policy of Shopify, Inc. will prevail with respect to all credit card transactions. .
We will use software which will have security encryption capabilities that will be applied to your Personal Information. The Website will have an easily accessed page on which you will be able to request us to delete your Personal Information and/or to unsubscribe from our advertising/information emails.
By using the Website you are consenting to the collection and use of the information you provide to HALCRAFT subject to these Terms and Conditions.
5. Products, Prices and Service
Prices for our products and services are subject to change at any time without notice.
We reserve the right at any time to modify or discontinue any product or service appearing on the Website without prior notice.
We shall not be liable to you or to any third-party for any modification, price change, suspension or discontinuance of any part of the Website.
We do our best to have the colors of our products accurately represented on the Website; however, differences in ambient lighting, monitors, monitor resolution, graphics cards, ISP transmission rates and methods and other mean we cannot guarantee that the color you see is exactly the color of the item represented.
You agree to provide current, complete and accurate information for all purchases made from the Website. You agree to promptly update your Personal Information, so that we can complete your transactions and contact you as needed.
You can review the most current version of these Terms and Conditions at any time at this page. At any time and in our sole discretion, we reserve the right to update, change or replace any part of these Terms and Conditions by posting updates and changes on this Website. It is your responsibility to check the Website periodically for changes. Your continued use of, and/or access to the Website following the posting of any changes, updates or additions to these Terms and Conditions constitutes acceptance of those changes, updates or additions.
6. Returns, Refunds & Exchanges
(A) To be eligible for a refund or exchange, you must follow the instructions which appear in this paragraph of these Terms and Conditions.
(i) You must obtain a return authorization number by requesting the same by sending an email to Returns@Halcraft.com. In order to obtain the return authorization number, your request must be made within thirty (30) days of purchase and you must identify the items for which you are seeking a return authorization by order number. If your request does not include all items included in a particular order number, you must also provide an accurate description of the particular items you wish to return.
(ii) You must follow the shipping instructions contained in the return authorization email.
(iii) When we receive the returned item, we will inspect the same, and if it is unused, in the same condition that you received it, and in the original packaging, we will determine whether the item being returned has a defect caused by us, a manufacturer or our shipper, and if that is the case, we will have the right to exchange the returned item with the same or similar items in new condition, or we may choose to provide you with a credit as set forth in subparagraph (vi) below.
(iv) If we determine that the defect was not caused by us, a manufacturer or our shipper, at our sole discretion, we may reject your return request, or we may provide you with a credit or partial credit, or otherwise deal with your return request.
(v) After we have inspected the returned item and made a determination regarding the course of action we will take, we will notify you of our decision by email.
(vi) If your return request is approved, your refund will be processed, and a credit will be issued only to the credit card you used to make your purchase and we will notify you when we authorize our agent to provide the credit.
(vii) If you wish to exchange items you purchased for other items for sale on the Website, and if you can return the originally purchased items unused, in the same condition that you received it, and in the original unopened packaging, please follow the return process. We will communicate by email with respect to an exchange request in order to try and satisfy your request.
(B) The following items are not returnable; gift cards, and items which marked “On Sale” or “Final Sale”.
(C) If you have any questions about returning or exchanging an item, please send an email to halinfo@Halcraft.com and please be sure to include your order number and be as specific as possible.
7. Links
The Website may contain links to other websites which are owned and operated by third parties. HALCRAFT is not responsible for the operation of those websites. If you click on any link, you do so at your own risk. The fact that a third party has placed a link on the Website with our consent does not mean that we are making any representation about the content on that third party website or about the security precautions (or lack thereof) on that third party website. If you are concerned about the security issues involving accessing a third party website we would advise you not to access that website without advice from a computer expert of your own choice. We cannot provide advice regarding these kinds of security issues.
8. Remedies, Disputes and Damage Limitations
For any actual or threatened breach of these Terms and Conditions, you agree that HALCRAFT shall be entitled to specific performance or injunctive relief, or both, in addition to monetary damages to which HALCRAFT may be legally entitled, together with reasonable legal expenses and disbursements.
With regard to the sale of any goods or services to a Website purchaser, the maximum liability of HALCRAFT shall be the amount paid for the goods and services plus any shipping expenses and sales or use tax charged to the purchaser. HALCRAFT shall not be liable for special, exemplary or punitive damages, nor shall HALCRAFT be liable for personal injury or death caused by misuse of any product.
These Terms and Conditions are governed by the laws of the State of New York without considering its conflicts of laws doctrines. You and HALCRAFT agree that the courts sitting in Westchester County, New York, shall be have sole and exclusive jurisdiction over any dispute between you and HALCRAFT or any claim you make against HALCRAFT.
If HALCRAFT contracts the operation and or administration of the Website to a third party, the provisions of this paragraph of these Terms and Conditions shall apply to that third party contractor in the same manner and to the same extent as the provisions of this paragraph of these Terms and Conditions apply to HALCRAFT.
9. Errors and Omissions.
Occasionally there may be information on the Website that contains typographical errors, inaccuracies or omissions relating to product descriptions, pricing, promotions, offers, product shipping charges, transit times and availability. At any time, without prior notice, (including after you have submitted your order), we reserve the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions and to change or update information or cancel orders if any information on the Website or on a related website is inaccurate.
10. Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless HALCRAFT, our subsidiaries, affiliates, partners, officers, directors, agents, contractors, licensors, service providers, subcontractors, suppliers, interns and employees harmless from and against any claim or demand made by any third-party due to or arising out of your breach of these Terms and Conditions or the documents incorporated herein by reference, or your violation of any law or your violation of the rights of a third-party.
11. Severability
In the event that any provision in these Terms and Conditions is determined by a court with competent jurisdiction to be unlawful, void or unenforceable, such provision shall nonetheless be enforceable to the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, and the unenforceable portion shall be deemed to be severed from these Terms and Conditions, and such severance shall not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions.
12. Termination
The obligations and liabilities of you and HALCRAFT incurred prior to the termination date of these Terms and Conditions shall survive the termination of these Terms and Conditions for all purposes.
These Terms and Conditions shall be effective unless and until terminated by either you or us. You may terminate these Terms and Conditions at any time by notifying us that you no longer wish to use our Services, or when you cease using our site.
We may terminate these Terms and Conditions at any time without notice and you will remain liable for all amounts due up to and including the date of termination.
13. Entire Agreement
Our failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of these Terms and Conditions shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision at any time.
These Terms and Conditions are posted by us on the Website and it constitutes the entire agreement and understanding between you and HALCRAFT governing your use of the Website and the purchase of any product or service from the Website. These Terms and Conditions supersede any prior or contemporaneous agreements, communications and proposals, whether oral or written, between you and us, (including, but not limited to any prior versions of these Terms and Conditions).
If you purchase any product or service from the Website your credit card transaction will be processed by Shopify, Inc., and will be subject to the Privacy Terms posted by Shopify, Inc. at https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy
Any ambiguities in the interpretation of these Terms and Conditions shall not be construed against HALCRAFT.
14. Contact Information
Questions about these Terms and Conditions should be sent to us at Halinfo@halcraft.com.
*To receive 20% off your purchase of over $25 of non-sale items.
© 2020 Halcraft Collection - Owners & Creators of Bead Gallery™.
Dedicated to finding new and exciting beads and components to help you flourish as a DIY beading and jewelry making artisan.
Powered by Shopify
translation missing: en.cart.ajax_cart.loading...
translation missing: en.wishlist.ajax_wishlist.go_to_wishlist
translation missing: en.cart.ajax_cart.close
EN ES
